Justice shall be ours. Princess Asalem sought only to make of herself a bridge to peace. Her death must be avenged. This situation demands that we orbital knights deal the cowardly Terrans a crushing blow. Spilling the blood of these wretched earthlings will be our tribute to her highness.
All right. Easy now. Let's go.
That was so scary. I thought I was going to step right on him.
That would have gotten you docked more than a few points.
That wasn't funny at all. Isn't that right, little sister?
Kisaki, I really wish you'd stop that.
Can you climb down all right?
Yes.
I can. Thank you very much.
I can.
綺麗なものは綺麗なままで守り続けたいと思うよ
空と水が星を染めて 淡く虹を描いて散って
眩しい夜 君が歌う声は どこまで届くのだろう
憂えの澄まう青い星の光 ただ僕らは恋をして
たったひとつの未来のために 今のすべて奏でてみる
飛び立つよ 瞬くない空へ
What was that?
So then that's what it was All the radar showed was meteor-like masses
向上から雲とイワラ
A full meteor attack J.D.M.O. those damn Moshiens ruim
We barely made it out of there.
You're safe.
I am.
Thank you, Adelritzo.
Things are well here.
Oh, yes.
Everyone is okay.
Good.
Wonderful.
That was nice work out there now.
Thanks, Yuki.
Honestly, you did a great job.
Though I'm pretty sure we can chalk it up to the tireless effort and guidance of your good-natured, beautiful instructor.
I'm so proud of you.
And you too.
Nina!
Oh, Inko!
You guys came back to rescue us!
Yeah, but I didn't see your names on any ferry passenger manifest.
That's a relief, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's kind of hot.
Ugh.
The city.
It's gone now, isn't it?
Yeah.
Then I would guess that we're next.
No way.
We're gonna get through this.
Count on it.
If that's the case, then you might want to try not running into that.
Right or left or left or right or...
Just vent the skirt.
Hey, just what does that helmsman think he's doing?
Pardon me.
Yes?
I wanted to thank you.
Uh...
Inaho.
Inaho Kaizuka.
Inaho, my thanks for saving me.
My name is...
You can call me Salem.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Well, thanks, Salem.
You too.
If you wouldn't mind, perhaps you could show me around this vessel.
Hmm.
Is that okay?
Mm-hmm.
But, milady, you...
It's all right.
Let's try once more.
My name is Asalem vs. Ellusia.
I'm Emperor vs. Granddaughter.
So then, this is the real you?
Before, it was a holographic likeness.
A kind of optical disguise.
But I saw the princess assassinated.
During the parade, I saw the whole thing.
She was...
She was a double.
Her highness was not well enough to be there as she wished to that day.
The security detail leader insisted that her appearances had to be maintained.
It really was a double then.
When my grandfather, the Emperor, learns that I am still alive,
this war will come to an immediate end.
So we cannot delay any further.
I must get in touch with Verse.
But how?
At this stage, that won't be very easy.
They're still jamming our radio signals,
and the Internet's been destroyed along with everything else.
What we can do is take you to a facility where the Verse government can be contacted.
I'll need to speak with my sister, Yuki.
You can't do that!
We know that Verse has spies among you that are here on Earth.
They had to have worked with the assassins.
Whoever they are, we know they want Her Highness dead.
I'm sorry we have made you a part of this problem.
It was not deliberate.
Now I beg you.
You must keep this between us.
Oh, I am so glad that we have you here, Dr. Yagarai.
I haven't used servo-assist therapy in a while, so don't try anything out of the ordinary, okay?
Remember, this is only temporary.
Oh, it's fine. This will do.
You may not feel pain now, but it is a strain on your system.
When the anesthetic wears off, you'll feel it.
Okay, I've got it. Don't worry.
I'll come in for some fine-tuning later, okay?
Oh.
Or maybe we should take care of those adjustments now.
It's sad about Okisuke.
Man, he was a dillweed up to the very end.
Dillweed, pervo, and a slacker.
Poor bastard tried to help, but died instead.
And now we dump on him.
Well, he shouldn't have got himself killed.
Inko.
They started a war and blew apart our moon.
That Heaven's Fall wrecked the whole damn planet for us.
They sit there in the satellite belt looking down on us.
They gotta pay for Okojo and every single person on Earth who's been killed.
Those Martian bastards.
So about earlier, what will you do?
Gonna keep her a secret?
When everyone knows an enemy could come at any time,
human beings aren't known for remaining very calm.
If they find out she's a Martian,
no telling what could happen to her.
You're a real softie, concerned about the enemy?
She is not our enemy.
The enemies are the people who tried to assassinate her.
If what she says is true,
then we've got to get her safely to the United Forces of Earth Headquarters.
What about you?
Rye.
My name is Rye Ariash.
What are you gonna do?
No guarantees.
If I believe that we're in danger,
I'll spill everything.
All Martians are the enemy.
Sir Trillram is dead, you say?
Yes, my lord.
In the meteor bombardment.
How dare they?
To think a knight would target my territory under the cover of battle.
Have they no honor as orbital knights with a common goal?
In time, I shall learn his identity and then punish him.
Bring Vlad to me.
Hunt down all the Terrans.
Turn this place to ashes.
We shall avenge her highness.
My lord.
Um, Princess of Salem is...
That's why I'm going to kill her
and make certain of it this time.
What is it?
Well, my lord.
Further devastation to an already conquered area.
Given Princess of Salem's sentiments might...
Wait.
Are you implying that you have the right to an opinion?
Huh?
Know your place here, Terran.
You think yourself worthy of doing battle for verse?
For 15 long years,
we orbital knights looked out from the shattered moon
to the earth.
Ever yearning for the day we would reach out and take it.
With her death,
our princess made that dream a reality.
This battle belongs to the orbital knights.
It does not concern you.
He's trying to exploit her death, too.
Ser Trollram was a long-time guest at Castle Cruteo.
If we let her stay alive,
my entire clan will surely be branded as traitors!
We...
This conspiracy has a ringleader.
Count Cruteo?
No, it can't be.
What do I do?
Power down engines.
Powering down, ma'am.
Captain Margvarege.
I'm glad you're safe.
We've been waiting for you.
Commander Nakabayashi.
Good to see you, sir.
Where's everyone else?
The assault craft Watatsumi is currently taking a longer, safer route.
The seas are a mess,
thanks to that unexpected meteor bombardment.
On Exo Mizusaki's orders,
we went ahead in landing craft one with Appaloosa platoon.
We are here to give you support and defend the refugees until the Watatsumi arrives.
That's a big help.
This place was abandoned.
Hmm?
Even though there isn't much evidence of damage to the general area.
Yes, ma'am.
A wise decision.
Digging in only makes damages worse later.
Makes sense to get out of here.
That's what I'd expect to hear from someone who lived through the war 15 years ago.
We'll wait for the Watatsumi to arrive.
Volunteer some hands to help with resupplying the landing craft.
Understood.
Hmm.
I'm gonna put these rations here.
Thank you.
Wow, we're not accustomed to seeing you help out like this, Calm.
Yeah, when we were doing military drills, you were always gone.
Yeah.
Well, that was then.
Now we'll do anything if it means wiping out the Martians.
I've scheduled us for a three-shift perimeter watch.
Did the Watatsumi check in yet?
They can't get through.
Jamming is too intense.
We can't get a signal within a few dozen miles.
We'll continue scanning for anything.
Okay.
Appaloosa leader, this is Appaloosa 3-3.
We've got a friendly here.
Looks like there's some damage.
Huh?
Appaloosa 3-3, report!
What's that?
It's an attack!
What the hell?
All hands, battle stations.
Yes, ma'am.
Prep LC-1 for immediate launch.
Everyone, get inside!
Appaloosa 3-3, report!
Enemy cataphract, single unit, bunker behind a building.
Currently engaging.
Surrounded.
Fire at will.
Take the flanks.
Hmph.
You're using projectiles.
Witness the power of my cataphract.
Behold the Argyre, and die.
Alt-NOA output approaching peak.
Energy flow at optimum.
Deploying blade field.
Alt-NOA drive output at maximum.
Plasma generator start up complete.
Blade drawn.
Open fire!
Is that a laser weapon?
Doesn't look.
Is that a sword?
Up?
Appaloosa 3-3!
Message from LC-1.
Go ahead and put it up on speaker.
Captain Mark Barrage!
What's your status?
Not so good, ma'am. And your end?
Fueling completed.
Refugee boarding is complete.
We'll ship out too.
Once we're out, we'll use our SSMs to finish it.
We'll regroup out at sea.
Damn, Mars Knight.
Get me a sick rep.
Damage to hull. It's minor.
It won't affect seaworthiness.
APU is offline.
We can't power up the engines.
I'll go look.
Me too.
Oh, great. What now?
Hey, wait! Calm!
It looks like the main engine's okay.
We'll do a temp fix.
That's not the same type as the one earlier.
Look there in its hand.
Is that a... sword?
How would I know what it is?
I must speak with that knight.
Oh no, m'lady, you...
It's too dangerous.
What if he's working with the assassins?
I know the risk.
But...
If that is the way to keep everyone safe here,
I must do it.
No, you were very lucky earlier.
You mustn't do anything to put yourself at risk.
Please, stay here.
Stay right here.
Inaho?
I'll buy us time.
You two get back inside.
Hey, I'm your friend, aren't I, man?
I'm gonna help!
Thanks.
Would you guys hang on a second?
I need you up there, Inko.
Up there?
Hmm.
Nice.
Yeah, I'm gonna help.
Okay, I'm gonna help.
Thanks.
Help!
Would you guys hang on a second?
I need you up there, Inko.
Up there?
Hmm.
Nice.
Training units.
Is that Inaho?
What's your progress?
We're gonna have to patch straight into the pressure tank.
Training units?
Is that Inaho?
What's your progress?
We're gonna have to patch straight into the pressure tank.
High explosive rounds no good, huh?
Let's try armor-piercing.
Quite clever.
Won't get a mid-air detonation if you don't use explosive rounds.
Nevertheless...
Looks like the tips are evaporating, throwing off trajectory.
The Leidenfrost effect, huh?
It's putting out a lot of heat.
Hmm.
A pincer attack, is it now?
No.
What's this?
Well, how quaint?
But in that primitive cataphract, how long can you last?
Time to say goodbye.
Just a little bit more to the right.
And bingo.
My main monitor's down.
Now, Kong.
Finally!
One more time!
No, you don't!
Yes, I do.
Who do you insects think you are?
Who do you insects think you are?!
Huh?
Sincere apologies for being so late, Captain.
It took quite a while for us to find a safe enough route.
Mizusaki, do you want to know why you have such trouble getting a date?
I thought I should be fashionably late, ma'am.
That's after you've already gotten a date.
The smoke is finally cleared. We can see the target.
Artillery, disarm fuses.
Cataphrac unit, take aim.
Now fire!
Come on!
We have pressure now!
Turbine speed is climbing!
Ignition!
Let's withdraw.
Roger!
They're getting away!
We'll meet again.
Whew. All according to plan, huh?
According to what?
What? That was really close back there.
This isn't like you to be so reckless, Inaho.
You think so?
Maybe you're right.
What is it now, Slain?
My lord, please allow me to avenge Princess Asalem.
As I recall, I told you, you are not worthy.
Be gone, Terran.
Please allow me...
Hmm?
To go into battle.
The world will last.
The world is 30 years later.
Stay with me.
Ahura!
Time's going to be so delicious, and this is like how I find it.
Tip two.
I can wake up in the world.
You must be called my control.
Most of your friends are already in the world.
Yeah.
The whole world is all about this world.
It also comes from the깃.
決めつけばかり 戻れを聴いた 自分は埃で踊だらけても
棚に隠した哀れな端に乗れた鏡の中
凄くの傷だけ干支って 手軽な強さで価値と全ок
Oh, do you think it's too far?
I say cry, yeah
I say rise, yeah
I say get the sky on the air
Don't say oh, oh, oh
I say, oh, oh
I say, I say, oh, oh
I say cry, yeah
I say, oh, oh
Let them back see that
The stars is beautiful
Let them reduce my house and hell and build me
Let them back see that
The stars is beautiful
Let them do you live through it's time and I'll be